Hello friends, I am Nitin Verma, I have
brought a very good informative
video for you. There is some information about
accidents and their claims.
When a car meets with an accident, the
customer
faces a lot of problems in the Play Store. He
makes many mistakes, due to which he is
not able to claim the claim. This causes a
lot of
trouble to the customer. Today we will give you
some basic information about
what steps you should take in case your car meets with an accident, so that you
can get your car successfully and easily repaired. If it is
a commercial vehicle of yours and the car meets with an accident,
after an accident, before claiming the accident, some
documents are required which are
from the cabinet.
I want to tell you about some such developments,
like the driver should have a diesel variant driving license, he should have a
double pass, he should have a permit, he should have a
challan. If the car is loaded, then a
challan is required.  If the vehicle is involved in a minor
accident, then it is an international accident.
In the area where the accident took place, an
intimation letter is given to the police station.
If there is an eye glass, then an FIR is filed. The FIR is
sent to the police station, a
copy of which should be kept with you. In ancient times and
religious places, after this, the
RC of the vehicle should be there, details and
insurance of the vehicle should be there.
Now insurance is also good, they
come after the average of the vehicle, they do
conference in these senses for some less money,
but they do not cover some dances in it,
like a hybrid 2327 da and your Anil
tap, all these which are advanced, can
give you very good returns during the time of travel, it is
in the dash of the vehicle,
otherwise what happens during vacation is that the
plane which you have is
used a lot in the rally, due to which the crops
benefit.
Hello friends, I would like to tell you that when
you are at your home, then what should you do at that time,
due to this,
what steps should you take if
your vehicle is a commercial traveler, commercial
vehicle, is going on the road, that Kavita has
ever told me about her  It is updated,
later what should you do in case of an accident,
first of all the vehicle is
here also, there is a toll free number in your policy, you can
call that free number and get
your team tested as insurance company,
its information
should be given to the insurance company immediately that our
vehicle has been damaged by acid here, secondary,
go to whichever police station is there, its donation is given as a gift, take it
from there like this, these are
two things with roti, after that our intimation gets
activated and you get the PIN number,
after that number the
insurance company depends on you,
which does the support survey,
where the vehicle is acid, who plays sports there,
how much time is in the vehicle, what is it,
I will tell you this, this is
how the support survey is done, the
support service is the actual condition of the vehicle at the
time of accident and the vehicle which is
there, when the invitation is made,
after the vehicle is made, it remains in Delhi, hence it is
very important, it does not get done on WhatsApp, the
customer and after it becomes functional, it is
more immediately parked there  In
which 25% of the player is deducted.
In this condition, the insurance company
deducts 125% of the plane's money. So
friends, never make this mistake. If there is an accident of the car, then get the
support survey done
immediately from the insurance company. They can
service for one or two days, which is
their limit and
whatever table time or trans is
available with them for taking the photo, they will get the support survey done by selling it. There is a
NAAC system in which your photo
is taken on the plot. After this, the car should be
taken to the workshop of Class Life.
After that, if your body goes to the workshop, now
what has to be done after this, this car has
reached the workshop of Kachhawa. After that,
I am going to tell you
nothing, children. If it goes, then the
entry of the car is done there. After the entry,
finally, the repair company of your
crush, to whom you took the car,
makes an estimate of the car. The estimate is done by the
insurance company and the trust of mutual trust of
comments. Whatever I have told you, you have to submit it in the customs.
You will be given in the top merit list.  I will give you that by
making an appointment for your appointment,
you will attend your system and
submit the amendment to the companies,
after that the insurance company will give an approval for the repair and
start the work, if it is weak for dismantling then
it will give you the order for dismantling
that you
can dismantle the vehicle, after tracking all the comments,
whatever is typed in this process is
taken by the company and this company took so much time from
you, after this
when the vehicle is registered, the
vehicle gets dismantled, after that the
surveyor of the insurance company comes again and
accesses if any additional repair is found in it, if there is any
damage to the vehicle from outside, then this much
time cannot be taken out actually, in
which after the investigation,
action things are taken out, Gandhi Kuchakra additional things can
also be added in it, they can be
disinvested, this
repair job starts,
after the repair the vehicle is dismantled, the final match is done,
heading in disgusting gas, if you are in cashless then
after paying the money for your dismantling, you can take away the vehicle
And if the car is not running properly and you are having
stomach ache, then you will have to get the
car released from there by making full payment
and
you can get it completed by submitting it to the insurance company, you can get a
break to complete this project and you
can also get complete updates of the car, if even after this you have any doubt then there
is a link below, comment in the comment box, if nothing can be done then
I will
definitely try to give you the answer.